- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Αα'
    Back: 'Alpha'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ββ'
    Back: 'Beta'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Γγ'
    Back: 'Gamma'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Δδ'
    Back: 'Delta'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Εε'
    Back: 'Epsilon'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ζζ'
    Back: 'Zeta'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ηη'
    Back: 'Eta'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Θθ'
    Back: 'Theta'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ιι'
    Back: 'Iota'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Κκ'
    Back: 'Kappa'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Λλ'
    Back: 'Lambda'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Μμ'
    Back: 'Mu'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Νν'
    Back: 'Nu'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ξξ'
    Back: 'Xi'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Οο'
    Back: 'Omicron'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ππ'
    Back: 'Pi'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ρρ'
    Back: 'Rho'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Σσς'
    Back: 'Sigma'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ττ'
    Back: 'Tau'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Υυ'
    Back: 'Upsilon'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Φφ'
    Back: 'Phi'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Χχ'
    Back: 'Chi'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ψψ'
    Back: 'Psi'

- type: Basic
  fields:
    Front: 'Ωω'
    Back: 'Omega'
